https://inlandbuildings.com/privacy-policy-2/

Skip to content800.438.1606 | 256.739.6827HomeDM LocatorContact UsUpper right minor navSearch: Search
HomeMetal BuildingsStructural SystemsRoof SystemsWall PanelsComponents & AccessoriesComponents Order FormCommercial IndustrialPanelsStructuralAccessoriesFlat SheetsTrimCIP CatalogStanding SeamPanelsStructuralAccessoriesTrimSSR CatalogAgri/ResidentialPanelsAccessoriesFlat SheetsTrimAR CatalogArchitecturalPanelsStructuralAccessoriesTrimAP CatalogColor SelectorColor ChartWarranty InformationInland Seamer RentalSales & ServiceDM LocatorEstimatingCredit ApplicationCustomer ServiceField ServicesProject PhotosAgriculturalAviationCommercialGovernment/CommunityIndustrialSelf StorageFor ArchitectsDetail DrawingsPanel InformationBuilding SpecificationsFlorida Product Approval NumbersFor BuildersBuilder LocatorField Problems & ClaimsAbout UsIntroduction to IBSHistory & TimelineLetter from the PresidentExecutive TeamOur CapabilitiesNews & EventsContact UsJoin Our TeamYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, Company Name or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.Do we use ‘cookies’?We do not use cookies for tracking purposesThird Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymouslyOnce this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:By emailing usBy calling usHow does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Inland Building Systems 2141 Second Avenue S.W. Cullman, Alabama 35055Telephone: 256-739-6827 Toll Free: 800-438-1606 Facsimile: 256-739-5657 Toll Free Facsimile: 800-438-1626 Email: sales@inlandbuildings.comLocate a DMNeed to find an IBS District Manager (DM) near you? Click here »Need a quote?Fill out our short Quick Quote form and we’ll get back to you as soon as possible. Quick Quote Form »CONTACT INFORMATIONToll free: 1.800.438.1606
Tel.: 256.775.3500
Fax: 1.800.438.1626 E-mail us »
Product DatasheetsCommercial & Industrial
Go to Top
